

Solo, Indonesia 081328081308 · jasonalhilal@gmail.com

Jason Al-Hilal Sabda Dewa, Computer Science Student

I'm an Indonesian-based web developer focused on crafting clean & user-friendly experiences, I am passionate about building excellent software that improves the lives of those around me.

Experiences

Web Developer at Anforcom event HMIF Undip

May 2021 - Present

I am responsible for working on a front-end web system to maximize user experience and good UI design for user satisfaction.

Website Staf at Staf Ahli Kominfo HMIF Undip

November 2020 - Present

- Updating information on the official website HMIF Undip.
- Updating and adding new features on the HMIF Undip website.
- Making and crafting user-friendly experiences on the IoS HMIF Undip website.
- Updating information of active members on the Databases Organization (DBO) website.

Web Developer at TEDx Undip

February 2020 — July 2021

I am responsible for working on a front-end web system and crafting user-friendly experiences on the 'Reveal the Sun' event TEDx Undip website.

Media Creatives Staf at DSC Undip

October 2020 — Present

Developer Student Clubs (DSC) are university-based community groups for students interested in Google developer technologies.

Software Development Division at I-RICH Undip

March 2021 — Present

I-RICH is a research center at the Informatics Department of Diponegoro University. I-RICH has several divisions such as Software development, Cyber Security, Business IT, etc.

Education

Bachelor Degree, Diponegoro University

January 2020 — Present

Computer Science, Faculty of Sciences and Mathematics

Links	Portfolio LinkedIn	<u>GitHub</u> <u>Instagram</u>
Skills	Git O JavaScript) MySQL
	O HTML & CSS	O 0